Yes, from the throat.
I thought it might be nice to spoil you once in a while.
Okay, great.
The Giant Dinosaur
Here it comes.
Why? Get some snacks.
Let's do this. Let's do this.
Buy some candy.
Buy some candy
We're at the hotel.
It's here, it's here, it's here.
Here we are!
We're staying at the Hotel Europa tonight!
I'm sorry.
Love, you wanted to stay here, didn't you?
I really wanted to stay here.
When I was little.
When I was little, we talked about it as a family.
It was a long-cherished wish.
Longing... It's amazing.
Amazing!
Melmane.
I don't know if you can tell.
But it's great.
I hope you get it.
It's great, isn't it?
It's amazing.
That's Big Ben.
That's not Big Ben.
Shall we go?
Let's go in.
Wow!
Oh, my God, Azizan.
It's true.
So pretty.
If it's a seasonal flower...
I love flowers.
Yes, you do.
They smell so good.
Smells great.
Wow.
It's gonna come out like this.
It's coming out.
It's like we're in a foreign country.
Oh, my God.
It's like a river.
Here you go.
Oh, wow.
Oh, I love it. Can we go up there?
It's cold right now.
Oh, there it is.
It's so cute.
I thought we were the only ones, but we're all lucky.
Oh, my God.
I'll open it.
Hello, there.
Meow, meow, meow.
Oh, no, no, no, no. Where are you?
Hmm?
It's still mixed up like this.
Can you help me?
It's hard.
You're doing great.
What? How did it open?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh!
Stylish.
Oh, my God.
Beautiful.
Oh, my God, what is that?
Oh, it's a passion red.
It's the Red Room of Passion.
Oh, my God.
The Passion Bedroom.
Wow, I just saw that.
What is that? Is that Big Ben?
I guess that's what it looks like when you say it.
Oh, my God.
I want to stay here today.
I'd like to go.
I wanted to go on a date
Huis Ten Mass.
It seems like you can enjoy the whole day there.
I've worked hard since this morning, so...
Good night.
Rest up and have fun tomorrow!
Good night, fist to fist
Good night.
After an overnight stay, we finally
Here we are in Huis Ten Masse!
Amazing!
That's great.
It's so nice!
The weather is too nice!
I really feel like I'm abroad.
The weather is so nice.
It's like we're abroad.
Can we go?
Let's go.
It's still mid-morning.
I'm sorry, but...
It's this sea star.
Amazing.
Not a cloud in the sky.
We've got it, don't we?
We're the sunny ones... the x2s.
Blow away the clouds!
Hey, there's a bear!
He's so cute!
So cute!
He's so cute.
I like bears.
I like them because of my mom's genetics.
Ever since I was little, my mom was like a bear charm.
I like things with bear motifs.
Like Tilly Bear.
That's nice.
There he is.
He's cute.
Super cute.
A bear.
It smells like flowers!
It smells like flowers.
It's kind of peaceful.
It's nice.
I'm healed today.
Soothing, right?
You're wearing a catsuit.
What? Bear sunglasses... super cute!
I like that.
Sunglasses.
Hinano and Konishi seem to like Miffy.
I want to buy some souvenirs.
What do you want? Can we go inside?
Is it okay to go inside?
Please subscribe to our channel.
What do you think?
Mippy's cute.
You know, the one with the rose is really cute.
The one with the rose is cute.
It looks like a butterfly.
Really?
It's very mature, but...
It's so cute!
I want to buy one for Konishi.
I want to buy it for him.
But I like blue. I want blue.
Hey, we who can't decide
I bought it
It's so cute.
There's something sitting on our heads.
Shall we go soon?
It's beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
It's Japan, but it doesn't look like Japan.
Is it that thing we flew over again?
Is it different? It looks like it, doesn't it?
No? Definitely not.
It's like it's invisible, but there's no one around to see it.
I like your pink flower.
They're prettier this way.
Cute!
What a cute little windmill!
Yay!
The front is amazing at this point!
Boo-boo! I'm really excited right now because I love flowers and I'm starting to wear a cap!
I'm so excited!
We're going to go to the park to get here.
That's nice.
So you can't go in here anymore?
Well, you can stay here forever.
You can stay here forever.
I'm into digital cameras today.
The year Hinano was born.
Where is it now?
Tokyo.
That's definitely a photo spot.
Wow, that's amazing.
Amazing?
It's so beautiful!
Surrounded by yellow
Happy black!
Wow.
Oh, my God!
Is that a real bird?
Is that real?
Real?
Like a real swan boat?
Is that real?
It's real!
That's amazing!
I saw it up close later.
Can I sit down?
Let's sit down.
Yay!
I'll be here for two hours.
I'll let you in.
I feel like I'm looking at you from my boyfriend's point of view.
Naturally.
Is that what Huis Ten Bosch is all about?
Look how cute it is.
It's so cute.
I want you to see this video.
I want you to show it to Hina's friends.
I want you to see it.
It's a Ferris wheel!
It's a Ferris wheel.
A big Ferris wheel.
I've been on that Ferris wheel.
You have?
I rode it with my family... my mom and I... she's so cute! You look just like her, don't you?
I wonder if that's true.
I was so surprised when I got to see her at the greeting concert.
It's okay if it's raining.
The famous one?
What's that?
What?
Mifi's umbrella.
Really?
Mifi in hiding?
Mifi in hiding.
I want to give her a load of chicks.
I've noticed.
I noticed.
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's this?
Oh, my God.
It's like a world record.
There's only one in the world.
It's some kind of three-story merry-go-round.
Wow!
Castle Carrousel.
Do you want to ride it?
I want to ride it.
I'd love to.
I'd love to ride it.
I haven't been on a merry-go-round since...
Not since the video for the photo book.
Okay, then.
About two years.
I haven't been on a merry-go-round since elementary school.
I haven't seen you in about three or four years.
I'm your favorite merry-go-round.
You do?
Surprisingly.
It's my favorite thing in Nagasaki. It's a party.
I'm not sure I'm allowed to enjoy it as much as I do. On the contrary.
For the stairs.
That's pretty high.
Ehhhh...
Nao-chan, get on the outside.
What about here? This is closer to the second row.
Sure, it's closer here.
Let's ride here.
Oh, I got it.
Yay, that feels good.
That feels good.
Here we go, Nobu.
First time in Japan.
Japan's first?
Japan's first.
We're off to the Sky Carousel!
Yay!
It's started!
That's great!
Up and down, up and down, up and down.
Bye-bye.
Oh, my God.
Throat.
She's so cute.
I look like her.
Pretty, pretty, pretty.
Beautiful here.
It's good.
Oh, my God.
Yay.
Pretty.
It's cute.
Fun
Pretty
Outrageous
You can only get so much here.
It's amazing.
That was fun. You must have really enjoyed the view.
How do you like it? I'm a sucker for a merry-go-round.
I've always wanted to ride one.
What's this? A flower shop?
What's this? Flower Fantasia
You can enjoy the flowers and fragrance.
Wow.
Wow. Look at this.
I'm working on it. The scent of flowers.
That's amazing. I'm so excited.
You like this kind of thing, don't you? I'm sure you do.
What is this?
Fragrance lab.
A petri dish is gently placed.
When you open it, the flower blooms and the fragrance spreads.
I'm pretty sure this is lavender.
It smells so good. It's coming from here.
Oh, my God.
It smells so good.
It smells like someone.
I can smell someone.
He's so cute.
Oh, my God.
If you stand in these footprints...
I'll find my flower in the horoscope.
Let's go.
I'll stand.
What is it?
Ominawashi.
protect there
Shishi
It's true, I'm a little rusty this morning.
Be on time
It's important to be punctual.
Have a good day.
Okay.
Is he leaving?
They're not responding.
It's not responding.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
Looks like it's going to be good.
Today's horoscope.
Yes...
I knew it! You're really not careful with my people.
I'm feeling a little sorry for myself.
Please choose one card of your choice.
Flower Shower
I kind of like this tulip, so I'll pick the tulip.
Okay, tulip.
Put this in the box.
In.
Ah!
It's so mysterious.
It's heavy.
Smells great.
Oh, my God.
What's this?
Oh, yes.
Oh, I'm in.
It smells so good.
Does it smell good?
Flower shower.
The way people are working together.
That's great.
See you later.
I'm off.
Dreams come true!
I'll go with this.
That's the language of the blue roses.
You want to sit down with this?
Oh, my God, you're right.
It smells so good.
This is what you get at a flower shower.
Oh, my God.
Is this what I think it is?
Am I the only one who's late?
There's a time difference.
Is there a time difference?
Let's go again.
Please.
Are you done?
Do you want to sit down?
Can I sit down?
Oh, here it comes!
Is it coming?
Yeah, it's glowing.
I don't really feel anything.
What happened?
I'll go first, then the human...
I'm gonna get that thing.
Here it comes!
What is it? Why?
I don't have any money.
Why don't you have any money?
Let's do this and keep the money.
Hey, Nao, we can go now!
Nao, why are you doing it a second time?
Why are you doing it a second time?
Next, let's go to Miffy's for dinner!
Miffy Cafe
Yay!
It's lunch time!
I'm so happy!
I'm so excited!
I've been meaning to tell you.
I've been coming to Mifi Cafe ever since we decided to go to Hanstenbosch.
I wanted to go to Mifi Cafe too.
Mineu is so cute.
I even ate Hina no Kumo and Konishi no Kumo...
This place is amazing.
My city
It's so cute. This building is so cute.
It's this Miffy flower clock.
It's real.
It's so cute.
The colors are cute.
It's cute.
It's a pretty color.
There's a building.
It's cute.
Hey, hey, did you see that? Right there.
It's Mickey.
He's so cute.
Tettelet.
Here he comes!
It's Miffy!
It's so Miffy!
Excuse me... that Melanie's fluffy hashed beef.
Soft and fluffy Miffy omelet with a drink.
So cute!
Oh, I ripped it... by mistake.
The hand towel is still cute.
I wonder what will happen when Hinano-chan comes.
She'll probably go crazy for peaches.
Maybe an omu-rice? I don't like it.
I love omu-rice.
It's all I love.
You've had nothing but your favorites since yesterday.
That's great.
I thought it'd be nice to be pampered once in a while.
Spoil him every day.
You're so cute.
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
What's this?
Oh, wait a minute.
Melanie's fluffy hash browns.
Wow.
Looks delicious.
It's so pretty. It's like a picture book.
What's this?
Mifi's omelette rice.
So cute!
Look at the cup!
A cup?
Isn't that a cup?
I want this.
I can't resist. I can't resist.
Well, let's have some, shall we?
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Delicious? You look really delicious.
Bon appétit, Melanie.
They're saying the same thing.
Delicious.
It's so soft and fluffy.
I want two more plates.
It's really good.
That's a pretty good endorsement.
How's it going lately?
50 years too long.
Naochan is at home playing video games all the time.
She loves music games.
If I don't play, I can't sleep.
I have to go fight.
I recently started playing Dead by Daylight.
I play it secretly at night.
Dead by Daylight is really fun.
You've seen it in action, right?
Most of the time.
Yeah, most of the time.
If you tell me most of the games...
I'd love to play a horror game with you sometime.
Let's do it.
I've always wanted you to play a horror game.
I've always wanted to play a horror game with you.
I'll watch over you on YouTube.
I'm doing it.
It's a channel.
The Haruu one, maybe.
I want to watch over him.
I want to watch over the game.
Maybe you'll be on there somewhere.
Please do!
I'll present it to you.
Thank you very much.
I'm feeling surprisingly full.
Two more dishes...
What?
It's oversweetened.
I'm so bad at buffets.
I'm not good at buffets.
Buffets...
You have to go get it yourself.
I have to go get it.
I'm really bad at it.
When I travel with my family, we usually eat in the room.
I thought, "Oh yeah, you do a lot of family travel.
We travel every year at the beginning of the year.
I didn't know that.
Really? I didn't.
We don't have a regular vacation except at the beginning of the year.
We sing together.
We're good friends.
Thank you for dinner.
We're so close.
I wanted to walk here.
Yesterday I was looking for a place where I could see.
Oh, yes.
That's great.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
Beautiful.
Wait a minute.
What, what, what? A little bit beautiful.
It's kind of beautiful.
I've only seen this on my summer vacation.
Beautiful! It's like a photo album.
It's like a photo album.
This is the Acacia.
We're going on this boat.
We're going down?
You're going down. You're going down.
Bye-bye.
A moment in Huis Ten Bosch.
We're going to a deserted island.
Hey, that's great.
Bye bye, Huis Ten Bosch.
I'm up.
It's almost time.
We're here.
An uninhabited island.
It's so bright.
I'm dressed like I'm not on a deserted island.
What am I going to do?
The water is so beautiful!
It's so clear!
The water is so clear!
It's a deserted island!
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha
Chushiki Island
Two wins, then. Fight the dinosaurs and find the cannon that lies on the island.
Yellow carnivorous dinosaurs, blue proliferating dinosaurs, red remaining dinosaurs.
Actually, there are some dinosaurs you can hit and some you can't.
You can get points by hitting the yellow carnivorous dinosaurs.
And in the end, you'll get points for your effort.
You'll get a ranking on this stage for the points you've earned.
So let's all do our best. Let's get started.
You ready?
Ready?
Follow the arrows until the screen turns red.
Let's keep going deeper and deeper into the forest.
Keep going in the direction of the arrow until the screen turns red.
It's fun!
This dinosaur is different.
I'm scared.
Where are you?
This one's different.
Oh, let's get a clear shot.
Oh, this one.
Good, good, good, good, good, good.
I got it.
That's great.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wonder if it's right. Where is it?
This isn't it.
Aah! There's something in there.
It's you! That's great!
Ouit-ouit.
Congratulations.
Farewell, as if you were going out.
We've killed five of them.
That's great!
They're here, they're here, they're here.
They're here.
On the ground.
Footsteps.
Dinosaurs!
What?
Hmm?
A little early.
It's a little early.
There's a big dent in it.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, that's hard, quick.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh no, he's so close!
Oh no, I'm out of ammo!
Oh, he's down!
Yay!
I got a very good tip! Wait a minute... this is fun!
I love this kind of stuff.
Where?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Where is it?
Oh no, the screen's acting up again.
It's yellow.
It's a giant dinosaur.
I'm out of bullets.
I think I hit my head.
Yes, sir.
Can't I just hit it once?
I got him! I got him!
Last Scot! Last Scot!
Let's check the screen, people!
Oh! He's through! It's definitely my shot!
OK!
Oh! I got so many points!
Finally, everyone made it!
Yay!
After the 5 points, support each other and send applause to Kenso!
Now, we will prepare the certificates for the top and the bottom!
The star mark is the 3rd place winner!
Yay! Thank you!
How did it work out for everyone?
25334 points! That's great!
Yay!
Let's have a round of applause for the third-place sister!
Oh! Yay!
Thank you!
That's great!
I'm so happy to get a certificate!
I haven't done this since junior high school.
Mr. Katoshi
Thank you for letting us spend the whole day at Huis Ten Bosch today!
That was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
We got to do a lot of things.
You know... really... really healed me.
I was healed all the time.
It was like nothing I've ever experienced.
That boat.
We went to a deserted island in about 40 minutes.
Tokyo
You can't experience that here in Tokyo.
It was very relaxing and fun. Thank you very much.
If you liked this video, please click the like button and the good button.
If you liked this video, please subscribe to my channel and click the "Like" button and the "Good" button!
Bye bye.
Bye bye!
Oh, the tableware is so cute!
The latte is super cute.
It's good for a pin, right?
I can use this for makeup.
You can use it for makeup.
Konishi-san and
Hinano-chan.
This one's cute, too.
No, but this girl...
This girl's cute, too.
This girl.
Let's take these two.
Konishi and Hinano-chan.
Good night.